National Organization for Women, New York State Chapter; Records apap029
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Feminist Publications Collection, 1970-2008; 7; 3.55 cubic ft.
  The NOW-NYS Feminist Publications Collection series contains periodicals and journals issued by a wide range of women's and feminist groups. Feminist publications include Speak Out (1972-1977), the Spokeswoman (1970-1977), and the Feminist Majority (1972-1998, with gaps), dealing with gay and lesbian rights, reproductive rights, abortion, rape and radical political ideology. The series also includes periodicals dealing with reproductive health care and civil rights such as Family Planning/Population Reporter (1975-1977) and Response to Violence and Sexual Abuse in the Family (1979-1981) Civil Rights Quarterly-Perspectives (1981).
  - Astraea Bulletin, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Books and Journals in Women's Studies, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Break Through, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Business Woman's Letter, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Campaign Report, 1987; 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Capital District Alive, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Center for the American Woman and Politics, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Choice-Planned Parenthood of Syracuse, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Citizen Action of New York, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights Quarterly- Perspectives, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Coalition Against Domestic Violence Newsletter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Comment, 1976; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Conscience, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Courage in Action, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Court Review, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - East-Hampton Star, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Empire State Report, 1976; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ex Femina, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Family Planning Perspectives, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Family Planning/Population Reporter, 1975-1977; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Feminist Majority, 1972-1975 (Oversized 7)
  - Feminist Majority, 1975-1978 (Oversized 8)
  - Feminist Majority, 1993; 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - The Feminist Press, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Feminist Publications - A-L, 1972; 1975-1976; 1979-1981; 2002 (Oversized 9)
  - Feminist Publications - M-Z, 1971-2006 (Oversized 10)
  - Feminist Teacher, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Feminization of Power, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Freedom Writer, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Generations of Women: In Search of Female Forebears, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Gospel According to Lilith, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Grand Jury Report, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Green Space, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Guttmacher Report, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Hispanic Women's Center, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Hooking Up, Hanging Out and Hoping for Mr. Right, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Hot Flash, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - The Impact of Violence in the Lives of Working Women Creating Solutions- Creating Change, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - In Brief, 1993; 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Instantes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Interact, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Journal of World Education, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Know Inc., 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Lesbian Feminist, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Momentum, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Monthly Extract: An Irregular Periodical, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Ms., 1987; 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - NARAL News, 1986; 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - National Center for Lesbian Rights, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - National Commission on America Without Roe, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - National Museum of Women in the Arts, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - National Women's Health Network, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Network News, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - New York Women, 1989; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - News on Women in the Government, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Not For Ourselves Alone, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - NYS NARAL Newsletter, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - On the Issues, 1987-1990; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Operation Rescue NewsBrief, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Peer Perspective, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Pennsylvania Commission for Women, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Planned Parenthood of Suffolk County Newsletter, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Planned Parenthood-World Population- Washington Memo, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Pro-Choice Idea, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Pro-Choice Report, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Progam Guide, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Quash, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Questions and Issues on Prostitution: What we need to know, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Reproductive Freedom in the States, 1993; 1998; Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Reproductive Freedom News, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Republican Woman, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Resourceful Woman, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Response to Violence and Sexual Abuse in the Family, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Rights of Pregnant and Parenting Teens, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - SANEnews, 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Sex Equity News, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Shadow Ministry for Women, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Sibling Information Network Newsletter, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Speak Out, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Speak Out, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Speak Out, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Speak Out, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Speak Out! The Pro-Choice Network Newsletter, 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The Spokeswoman, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Status of Women in New York, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - SUNY Albany Women's Connection, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Supporters of Silkwood, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Time, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Update on Women and Family Issues in Congress, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Veteran Feminists of Amenca, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - What Congress Didn't Tell You, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Who Decides?, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Women and Revolution, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Women and Welfare Watch, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Women in Government, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Women New York, 1975-1977; 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Women Office Workers Newsletter, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Women's Advocate, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Women's Building News, 1993; 1998 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Women's Caucus News, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Women's Monthly, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Women's Political Causus- Brookyln, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Women's Political Times, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Women's Recovery Network, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Women's Studies Newsletter, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Women's Unit, 1970-1972; 1974 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Correspondence, 1975-2010; 8; 2.2 cubic ft.
  This series includes correspondence between NOW-NYS members, national board members of NOW, and NOW-NYS presidents. Correspondence also includes letters to and from other organizations, as well as politicians.
  - Association of Black Women in Higher Education Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Christina P. Davis Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Congress (1 of 2), 1989-1994; 1997-2005; 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Congress (2 of 2), 1989-1994; 1997-2005; 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - County of Suffolk Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth Toledo Correspondence, 1996; 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Erima Vaughan Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence (1 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence (2 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence (3 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence (4 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence (5 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence (6 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence (7 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence (8 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence (9 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence (10 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence (11 of 11), 1975; 1981-2005; 2007-2010; Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Governor Mario Cuomo Correspondence, 1982; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Hillary Clinton Correspondence, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Human Rights Campaign Fund Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Intern Correspondence, 1988; 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Jaralyn Gibson Correspondence, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Judy Sanford Guise Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Julia Kruger Correspondence (1 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Julia Kruger Correspondence (2 of 2), 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Kathryn Lake Mazierski -NOW- NYS President (1 of 3), 1998; 2000-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Kathryn Lake Mazierski -NOW- NYS President (2 of 3), 1998; 2000-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Kathryn Lake Mazierski -NOW- NYS President (3 of 3), 1998; 2000-2004; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Kim Gandy Correspondence, 1989; 1992; 2003; 2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Knights of the Ku Klux Klan, Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Legal Defense and Education Fund Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Lois J. Shapiro-Canter -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (1 of 4), 1990-1993; 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Lois J. Shapiro-Canter -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (2 of 4), 1990-1993; 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Lois J. Shapiro-Canter -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (3 of 4), 1990-1993; 1995-2000 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Lois J. Shapiro-Canter -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (4 of 4), 1990-1993; 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Marcia Pappas -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (1 of 6), 1993-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Marcia Pappas -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (2 of 6), 1993-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Marcia Pappas -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (3 of 6), 1993-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Marcia Pappas -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (4 of 6), 1993-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marcia Pappas -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (5 of 6), 1993-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Marcia Pappas -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (6 of 6), 1993-2010; Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (1 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (2 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (3 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (4 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (5 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (6 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Marilyn Fitterman -NOW- NYS President -General Correspondence (7 of 7), 1987-1994; 2004-2005; Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Molly Yard Correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - No Fault Divorce Correspondence, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NOW -Foundation INC. Correspondence, 1991; 1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - NOW -NYS PAC Correspondence, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Noreen Connell General Correspondence, 1986-1989; 2003 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - NYS Board of Elections Correspondence, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - NYS National Abortion Rights Action League, 1989-1991; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Orange County NOW- Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Patricia Ireland -National Vice President Correspondence, 1987-1989; 1991; 1994; 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Planned Parenthood Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Peer Affiliate Correspondence, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Rockland County Correspondence, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Saratoga NOW Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sharon I. Fawley -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1991-1996; 1998; Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sharon I. Fawley -NOW- NYS President General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1991-1996; 1998; Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - South Suffolk Chapter Correspondence, 1991; 2001; 2005 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Suffolk County Human Rights Commission -Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Susan B. Anthony -Award Correspondence, 1990; 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Vice President Dan Quayle -Correspondence, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)